<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2024-07-27T22:04:19+01:00</updated>
  <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//</id>

  
    <title type="html">One for All Forest School CIC</title>
  

  
    <subtitle>A Forest School for Neurodivergent Folk</subtitle>
  

  

  
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Session Information</title>
      <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Session Information" />
      <published>2014-07-18T00:00:00+01:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
      <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//project-1</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://oneforallforestschool.org//">&lt;h3 id=&quot;session-information&quot;&gt;Session Information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; Fridays 11 AM - 1 PM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Hodshrove Woods in Moulsecoomb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Course Dates:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fridays 11 AM-1PM April 19th to June 7th&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Location - Hodshrove Woods Moulsecomb&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special 6-Week Summer Evening Sessions!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mondays 6:00 - 8:00&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;July 22nd to August 26th&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Location - Bevendean Community Garden&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update for September 2024&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are full for our Monday Evening sessions and as these are now underway, we are unable to take on participants for this course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From September 2024 we hope to run monthly Forest School taster workshops across the city. Please keep a look out for the dates on social media or contact us if you would like us to keep you updated. Our hope is that by accessing Forest School workshops, you will feel curious and excited about joining future 6-week courses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope to run further 6-week courses from May 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; We offer up to 12 spaces per course at £5 per session. We ask that this is paid up front for the block of 8 sessions as a one off payment of £40 (or £30 for the 6-week summer evening sessions). If you think you may struggle to pay this amount up front please get in touch as we will do our best to work out a plan that works for you. We can offer concessionary spaces at half cost. Please get in touch if you feel this would be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name></name>
        
        
      </author>

      
        <category term="Web Development" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Session Information</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Forest School FAQs</title>
      <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Forest School FAQs" />
      <published>2014-07-17T00:00:00+01:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
      <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//project-2</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://oneforallforestschool.org//">&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-forest-school&quot;&gt;What is Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forest School is a learner-centred inspirational learning process, that offers opportunities for holistic growth through regular sessions. It is a long-term program that supports play, exploration and supported risk taking. It develops confidence and self-esteem through learner inspired, hands-on experiences in a natural setting. - Forest School Association&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-6-principles-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the 6 Principles of Forest SChool?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.Forest School is a long-term process&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.Forest School takes place in a natural wooded environment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.Forest School aims to promote holistic development&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.Forest School offers learners the opportunity to take supported risks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5.Forest School is run by qualified Forest School practitioners&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.Forest School uses a range of learner-centred processes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Forest School Association&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-makes-one-for-all-forest-school-different&quot;&gt;What makes One for All Forest School different?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One for All Forest School is currently only for adults (18+). We focus on making an inclusive environment for people with neurodivergent conditions such as autism, ADHD, dyslexia, CPTSD, Tourette’s Syndrome, personality disorders, etc. We pay particular attention to supporting participants with sensory, social, and emotional regulation differences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;who-are-the-forest-school-facilitaors&quot;&gt;Who are the Forest School facilitaors?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leah uses she/her pronouns. I am the founder and director of One for All. I am a qualified forest school leader and teacher. I also have experience as a disability social worker and as a family therapist. I have diagnosed ADHD and undiagnosed Autism. I am so excited to share the therapeutic benefits of being outdoors with you and the wonder of “play”. My favourite tree is an oak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kira uses she/her pronouns. I grew up in the Sussex countryside and have always felt a deep connection to nature and the outdoors. I joined One for All to help with the business side of things and now am excited to help run sessions and use my love of nature to help people reconnect with our planet and the outoodrs. My favourite flower is jasmine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-would-i-do-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What would I do at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Forest School there is a focus on learning through play (whatever that means to you). You might want to cook, craft something, go on a nature walk, journal, meditate, use tools, sit around the fire, tell stories, make a shelter or den, use your imagination, learn bushcraft skills, draw something, socialize, and much more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-do-i-wear-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What do I wear at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That depends on the weather. If it’s sunny you should bring a hat and suncream. If it’s rainy/wet you should bring waterproof clothing and boots. In the winter make sure to wear lots of layers as well as waterproofs. Don’t wear wellies in the winter - they’re not warm enough. Throughout the year you should wear comfortable clothing and close-toed shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-if-theres-bad-weather&quot;&gt;What if there’s bad weather?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forest School usually runs rain or shine. If it’s cold, we might do an activity to warm up or gather around the fire. If it’s raining, we will put up tarps to shelter under or enjoy some games in the rain! Likewise, if it’s very warm and sunny we will find areas of shade to cool off. This is why it’s important to be properly dressed for Forest School. We do not have sessions if it’s very windy or if there’s threats of lightening, though. That wound’t be safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;where-do-we-have-forest-school&quot;&gt;Where do we have Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have had sessions at a few differnt sites. We were first welcomed at Moulsecoomb Place which is a nice open area off Lewes Road. We found a home at Hodshrove Woods deep in the middle of Moulsecoomb. We have also explored Bevendean Woods near the allotments as a potential site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-is-learning-assessed&quot;&gt;How is learning assessed?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At it’s heart, Forest School is learner-led. We work collaborativly with you to set goals and track your development across 6 holistic domains: social, phsyical, intellectual, spiritual, emotional, and communcation. We will provide you with a “Learning Journal” with prompts, activities, and self-assessments that you can chose from to track your learning and growth. As leaders, we will provide you with supportive and constructive feedback too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-long-is-a-forest-school-session&quot;&gt;How long is a Forest School session?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forest School is a long-term programme so we ask that you try to commit to coming once a week for the 8 block of sessions. Sessions last 2 hours. The schedule for the sessions is fairly loose, but we try to start with Circle Time to welcome you and talk about any safety procedures, followed by free play time, and finally Together Time at the end to reflect and share together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;using-our-senses&quot;&gt;Using our Senses&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-might-i-see-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What might I see at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will see lots of different things in the Forest School setting. You might see the different types of trees we have on site such as ash, hawthorne, and sycamore. Depending on the season you might see differnt types of creatures such as butterflies, birds, or squirrels. You might want to stand back and look at the site as a whole or get up close with a magnifying glass and study details. It’s all about perspective!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-might-i-hear-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What might I hear at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’ll probably hear people chatting as they walk by and depending on the site, cars and buses as the drive by. But don’t let that distract you from the sounds of nature. If you listen, you’ll hear birds chirping, the breeze as it rustles the trees, and the crackling fire. You may even be able to identify the birds and other creatures you’ll hear. Storytelling is an important feature in Forest School so you might hear stories or songs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-might-i-feel-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What might I feel at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might feel the sun or the rain. You might feel warm or cold. You might feel “just right”. You might feel the grass underfoot or the breeze on your face. There’s lots of textures of differnt plants, materials, and creatures you might choose to explore. You might like that deep pressure and want to hug a tree or  You might like other sensations and want to swing in the hammock. There’s something for everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-might-i-taste-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What might I taste at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we’re doing a cooking session, you’ll taste some wonderful things at Forest School!  We might have some popcorn over the fire or some fruit for a snack. We might go on a little forage and use some of our harvest to make a snack. We have a general rule though - no pick-y, no lick-y. So unless you show the foraged goodie to at least 2 others who can confirm it’s edible, it’s best to primiarily use our other sesnses in Forest School.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-might-i-smell-at-forest-school&quot;&gt;What might I smell at Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on the season, you might smell a variety of things. In the spring and summer you might smell flowering plants. In the autumn, you might be able to smell the change in the air as it cools down. You might even smell the rain. Did you know humans have a very good smell for rain? We can smell the bacteria in the soil that’s activated after rainfall. This was likely a benefit for our ancestors who could smell good, rich soil for farmable land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-holistic-domains-of-learning&quot;&gt;6 Holistic Domains of Learning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-physical-benefits-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the physical benefits of Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with tools and crafts in Forest School develops motor skills and  coordination. Many activities in Forest School also promote physical wellbeing and help us develop our self-care skills. There is evidence to suggest that nature is a sensory regulating environment, and throughout the Forest School sessions you will be encouraged and supported to understand your sensory needs and preferences and activities that make you feel good in yourself!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-mental-benefits-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the mental benefits of Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Forest School, we understand the benefits of risk-taking and support you with calculating risks and developing your critical thinking skills. The activities you engage in will require you to build your concentration and perseverance which can be tricky things to develop in an age of instant gratification.  These activities will also stimulate your creativity and imagination as well as deepen your knowledge of the natural world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-emotional-benefits-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the emotional benefits of Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The activities and games you engage with in Forest School will help build your confidence, resilience, and ability to problem solve and cope with challenges. As we experiment and play, things might not always go the way we expect. Forest School gives us a safe and supportive place (in a naturally regulating environment) to explore those challenges and develop ways to emotionally regulate when things don’t go to plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-social-benefits-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the social benefits of Forest SChool?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Games and activities in Forest SChool give us opportunites to interact and socialize with each other. Participation and involvement can look different, depending on the person, but througout the sessions you will be building relationships with each other and with the Leaders. Part of the therapeutic nature of Forest SChool is the richness of those relationships, which is why we keep ratios and groups small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-spiritual-benefits-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the spiritual benefits of Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Spiritual” means different things to different people. In forest school, we like to think of it as a sense of awe, wonder, and connection to nature. We might also think of within the context of our morals, values, and ethics. In Forest School, we think of “play” as a spiritual practice. “Play” is an important part of Forest School and essential for all humans - no matter their age. Play helps us feel that sense of awe and wonder and gives us opportunites to play out our morals and values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-are-the-communication-benefits-of-forest-school&quot;&gt;What are the communication benefits of Forest School?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forest School is a great space to develop communication tools and strategies - both verbal and non-verbal. During the sessions you will likely practice communication skills involving negotiaton and cooperation. We often play games and do activities that help us thoughtfully and deliberately use verbal and non-verbal communication skills to tune into each other, listen, and communicate effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name></name>
        
        
      </author>

      
        <category term="Web Development" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">What is Forest School? Forest School is a learner-centred inspirational learning process, that offers opportunities for holistic growth through regular sessions. It is a long-term program that supports play, exploration and supported risk taking. It develops confidence and self-esteem through learner inspired, hands-on experiences in a natural setting. - Forest School Association</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Important Info and Policies</title>
      <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Important Info and Policies" />
      <published>2014-07-16T00:00:00+01:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
      <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//project-3</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://oneforallforestschool.org//">&lt;h3 id=&quot;policies-and-procedures&quot;&gt;Policies and Procedures&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggPZe6oG1m8wB6Y8?e=e1udXR&quot;&gt;One for All Forest School Handbook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggLyh3jxHH3CBv5Q?e=hV0hOh&quot;&gt;One for All Forest School Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJughSyHgD_QQOR9b8j?e=y7qpJP&quot;&gt;One for All Forest School Equality, Diversity, and Inclusion Policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJughZvmMb45aio1Vy_?e=25GHwO&quot;&gt;One for All Forest School Safeguarding Policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggX06RTfPTLJWfv_?e=VTNOof&quot;&gt;Moulsecoomb Place Emergency Procedures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJughIsJ3eLPYTZoMZE?e=urfitJ&quot;&gt;Hodshrove Woods Emergency Procedures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;risk-assessments&quot;&gt;Risk Assessments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggDXypekPbJO_ITk?e=4inKsD&quot;&gt;Moulsecoomb Place Site Risk Assessment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggEy3WWVI0z8-Nwn?e=1gBV34&quot;&gt;Working with Fire Risk Assessment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJugg4Ei5MDoZwE7x7X?e=y1YYlF&quot;&gt;Cooking Risk Assessment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggcFyuxuyeO0SXKJ?e=Pgz22Q&quot;&gt;Foraging Risk Assessment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggT1rQ2ys-XW7_hi?e=3gLR3n&quot;&gt;Using Saws Risk Assessment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://1drv.ms/w/s!AqZeykDJpLJuggYomXujq-FSmWvH?e=PkrHSE&quot;&gt;Using Ropes Risk Assessment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name></name>
        
        
      </author>

      
        <category term="Web Development" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Policies and Procedures</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Feedback</title>
      <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Feedback" />
      <published>2014-07-15T00:00:00+01:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
      <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//project-4</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://oneforallforestschool.org//">&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-brought-you-to-one-for-all-forest-school&quot;&gt;What brought you to One for All Forest School?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Getting to be in nature. It’s something I love but find it can be hard to motivate myself. The group being aimed at neurodiverse adults and I like the name. (Usually) only hear of Forest School in relation to children.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I have heard of Forest School for kids and always thought it would be cool to learn more about the natural world and take safe risks. I also really appreciate the opportunity to be in touch with the seasons and to be with other neurodivergent adults.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I very recently discovered I was autistic and was looking to meet people I could relate to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Time outside and in nature, a chance to be creative in an accepting group. It sounded inclusive and I know it’s good for me to try new things.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;surveys-and-feedback-forms&quot;&gt;Surveys and Feedback forms&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=DQSIkWdsW0yxEjajBLZtrQAAAAAAAAAAAAMAAFpFrPdURUExWjdQTTkxSVRQVUlTV1RaS0NBTDJJSi4u&quot;&gt;One for All Forest School Survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=DQSIkWdsW0yxEjajBLZtrQAAAAAAAAAAAAMAAFpFrPdUQVVaMVg5TDFESEQ1QUo0NjFOTTdINFZOTi4u&quot;&gt;One for All Forest School Feedback Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name></name>
        
        
      </author>

      
        <category term="Web Development" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">What brought you to One for All Forest School?</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Resources</title>
      <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Resources" />
      <published>2014-07-14T00:00:00+01:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
      <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//project-5</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://oneforallforestschool.org//">&lt;h3 id=&quot;websites&quot;&gt;WEBSITES&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website has useful ADHD and Autism self-assessments&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://embrace-autism.com/&quot;&gt;Embrace Autism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This webiste, developed by an Autistic person, is useful for understanding Autism&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://autismunderstood.co.uk/&quot;&gt;Autism Understood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This webiste provides information about Monotropism - a theory of Autism developed by Autistic people&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://monotropism.org/&quot;&gt;Monotropism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;research&quot;&gt;RESEARCH&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AWAKE Project has the most extensive collection of research articles about Neurodivergence we’ve found including EDS, POTS, ASC, ADHD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/118uYJvAfg09bnhKXn4Gc2Sv7-MR72EB2&quot;&gt;The Awake Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lovely article about Autistic people’s experiences of nature during the Covid-19 Pandemic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC10140763/&quot;&gt;Respite and connection:Autistic adults’ reflections upon nature and well-being during the Covid-19 pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;resources&quot;&gt;RESOURCES&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sensory-Motor Preferences&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.swbh.nhs.uk/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Childrens-Therapies-Sensory-Motor-Preference-Checklist.pdf&quot;&gt;Adult Checklist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beacon House - Trauma-Infomred Lens&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://beaconhouse.org.uk/resources/&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Woodland Trust&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.woodlandtrust.org.uk/blog/2020/03/tree-id-kids/&quot;&gt;Tree ID Resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name></name>
        
        
      </author>

      
        <category term="Web Development" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">WEBSITES</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Sign up Information</title>
      <link href="https://oneforallforestschool.org//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sign up Information" />
      <published>2014-07-13T00:00:00+01:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
      <id>https://oneforallforestschool.org//project-6</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://oneforallforestschool.org//">&lt;h3 id=&quot;interested-in-signing-up&quot;&gt;Interested in signing up?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please provide us with a little information about yourself!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below you will find two links to forms. One form takes you to the Contract that allows us to provide you with a service. The other link takes you to the Supporting You Form where you can let us know how we can suport you with the most comfortable and enjoyable experience possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These forms usually take about 5 minutes each to complete. Please contact us if you would like to complete the forms on paper or need support with completing the forms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;link-to-the-contract&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=DQSIkWdsW0yxEjajBLZtrQAAAAAAAAAAAAMAAFpFrPdUMEgzSDFVWlM2MlQ3TE5aNjNSOTVUNUZaQy4u&quot;&gt;Link to the Contract&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;link-to-the-supporting-you-form&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.office.com/r/SAJpcd3Bcc?origin=lprLink&quot;&gt;Link to the Supporting You Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name></name>
        
        
      </author>

      
        <category term="Web Development" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Interested in signing up? Please provide us with a little information about yourself!</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
